Contact

amcourson09@sbcglobal.net

www.linkedin.com/in/angelicacourson-6b6895130 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Customer Service Leadership Microsoft Word

Languages

Spanish (Elementary) English Italian (Elementary)

Angelica Courson

Full Stack Web Development at The University of Texas Austin

Summary

Experienced Customer Service Specialist with a demonstrated history of working in the retail industry. Skilled in Microsoft Word, Leadership, Microsoft Excel, Microsoft PowerPoint, and Microsoft Access. Strong support professional with a Bachelor's degree focused in Communication and Media Studies from University of Missouri-Columbia.

Experience

The Home Depot
Customer Service Associate
November 2020 - March 2021 (5 months)
Hutto, Texas, United States

Life Time Inc.

Kids Academy Team Member August 2020 - November 2020 (4 months)

Austin, Texas Metropolitan Area

Pella Windows & Doors of North Texas Accounting Intern December 2019 - January 2020 (2 months)

- Austin, Texas, United States
- Helped organize the office to make sure it was an effective working space.
- Used QuickBooks to create and pay bills.
- Helped assist the accounting department in preparation for auditing.

SAL

Study Abroad Student January 2019 - June 2019 (6 months) Milan, Italy

During my time abroad I got to live in Italy and experience Italian culture first hand. I took a number of courses that helped me understand the fashion industry as well as the production design industry including: Brand Identity, Design Methodology, Italian Design History and Visualization and Layout. I also experienced Milan Fashion week as well as Product Design week and got to work on creative projects to meet brand standards as well as create new products for the market.

MU Libraries
Digitization Assistant
February 2018 - August 2018 (7 months)
Ellis Library

- · Utilized Photoshop to edit digital files.
- · Handled delicate documents.
- Completed scanning and editing in a timely manner.
- Helped projects stay on track.

Winding Road Racing Accounting Intern June 2017 - 2018 (1 year) Austin, Texas Area

- Helped the accounting department with organization.
- Entered and paid bills.
- Organized supply closets.
- Checked the mail and sent out invoices and checks.

Education

University of Missouri-Columbia

Bachelor's degree, Communication and Media Studies · (2018 - 2020)

Baylor University

Bachelor's degree · (2016 - 2018)

The University of Texas at Austin

Full Stack Web Development · (2020)